<song artist="Rush" tile="Tom Sawyer">
    A modern-day warrior
    Mean mean stride
    Today’s Tom Sawyer
    Mean mean pride

    Though his mind is not for rent
    Don’t put him down as arrogant
    His reserve, a quiet defense
    Riding out the day’s events –
    The river

    What you say about his company
    Is what you say about society
    -Catch the mist – Catch the myth
    -Catch the mystery – Catch the drift

    The world is the world is
    Love and life are deep
    Maybe as his skies are wide

    Today’s Tom Sawyer
    He gets high on you
    And the space he invades
    He gets by on you

    No, his mind is not for rent
    To any god or government.
    Always hopeful, yet discontent
    He knows changes aren’t permanent –
    But change is

    What you say about his company
    Is what you say about society
    -Catch the witness – Catch the wit
    -Catch the spirit – Catch the spit

    The world is the world is
    Love and life are deep
    Maybe as his eyes are wide

    Exit the warrior
    Today’s Tom Sawyer
    He gets high on you
    And the energy you trade
    He gets right on to
    The friction of the day
</song>
<song artist="Gorillaz" tile="Empire Ants">
    Oh joy's arise
    The sun has come again to hold you
    Sailing out the doldrums of the whole week
    The polyphonic prairies here, it's all around you
    It's all around you, out here
    And if the whole world is crashing down
    Fall through space out of mind with me
    Where the emptiness we leave behind on warm air rising
    Blows all the shadows far away
    The falling alcohol empire, is here to hold you
    Rolling out and haunted 'til it sleeps
    Little memories, marching on
    Your little feet, working the machine
    Will it spin, will it soar
    My little dream, working the machine
    Soon like a wave that pass will fall
    And closing in on you they're going on
    Little memories
    Your little feet, working the machine
    Will it spin, will it soar
    My little dream, working the machine
    Soon like a wave that pass will fall
    And closing in on you they're going on
</song>
<song artist="Everything Everything" tile="Qwerty Finger">
    We slide in from the epoch of Anglo American wire
    And a Saxon spire,
    Glint in the glare far above me,
    Put pressure on it!
    She collapse me!
    Man alive, her every ache a baton to me!
    Age of ending!
    Where's the worth in proving I was here?
    But maybe Qwerty can leave some little evidence while he lives
    And all be lying in rows they can't believe that it's happening
    And Qwerty Finger replies "I don't know how to sleep knowing this"
    I can't go down like the rest, Oh Qwerty take it away!
    (if it's gonna happen to him)
    So how will they remember us whole, when we turn into salt?
    And it's mine, the fault, mine the dream, and the vein,
    Home of whale-flesh, make soap out of it!
    I regret so! Every wand I splinter in a fit of frenzy
    Distant memory! She don't care for leaving anything behind
    But maybe Qwerty can leave some little evidence while he lives
    And all be lying in rows they can't believe that its happening
    And Qwerty Finger replies "I don't know how to sleep knowing this"
    I can't go down like the rest, Oh Qwerty take it away!
    (then it's gonna happen to him)
    I can't let you turn yourself off.
    Off.
    Your every ounce an element sleeping,
    A part of you just never quite receiving,
    I wanna be the one to get in.
    But the only way you tell me you're certain,
    To draw asunder every leper curtain,
    Would be a hail of every flower to ash.
    And when every attosecond means nothing,
    And all that you believe in isn't working,
    I can't begin to tell you I know.
    And in 20, 000 years they trawl the seaboard,
    But all that's washing up there is a keyboard,
    Yeah they piece it all together from that.
    Come on, child, what you say,
    What you do, yeah it's all over now
    Qwerty Finger no more! Qwerty Finger no more!
    I can't do what you ask me!
    Qwerty Finger no more! No more!
    She collapse me! Man alive,
    Her every ache a baton to me!
    Age of ending!
    What's the worth in proving I was here?
</song>